<ROM>
<RomName>AICP</RomName>
<VersionName>aicp_crackling_mm-11.0-UNOFFICIAL-20160529</VersionName>
<VersionNumber type="integer">20160529</VersionNumber>
<DirectUrl>
<![CDATA[
https://basketbuild.com/uploads/devs/HLEEGG/AICP%20crackling%20(Wileyfox%20Swift)/aicp_crackling_mm-11.0-UNOFFICIAL-20160529.zip
]]>
</DirectUrl>
<HttpUrl>
<![CDATA[
https://basketbuild.com/uploads/devs/HLEEGG/AICP%20crackling%20(Wileyfox%20Swift)/aicp_crackling_mm-11.0-UNOFFICIAL-20160529.zip
]]>
</HttpUrl>
<WebsiteURL>
<![CDATA[
http://4pda.ru/forum/index.php?s=&showtopic=730213&view=findpost&p=48160837
]]>
</WebsiteURL>
<DonateURL>
<![CDATA[
https://google.ru
]]>
</DonateURL>
<Android>6.0.1</Android>
<CheckMD5>df0e11e52af92eeef5af34bd3e26507d</CheckMD5>
<FileSize type="integer">446481173</FileSize>
<Developer nil="true">HLEEGG</Developer>
<Changelog> <![CDATA[
====================
     05-29-2016
====================


   * packages/apps/PackageInstaller/
02d1a76 Merge "PackageInstaller: Initial DE translations by Ralf Luther" into mm6.0

   * packages/apps/Settings/
ae7526d Merge "Settings: Updated DE translations by Ralf Luther" into mm6.0

   * packages/apps/Stk/
f9aecea Stk: Make the text a little smaller
053ce97 Stk: Materialize message dialog icon
65aaf67 Change the theme and the style of the activities
a1e3c60 Fix tab/space inconsistencies in stk_msg_dialog.xml

   * vendor/aicp/
2285ea3 Merge "huashan: Adapt to device tree new fragmented structure" into mm6.0

====================
     05-28-2016
====================


   * frameworks/base/
f93ee94 appops: Respect screen interactivity before creating dialogs.
db231cd appops: Implement concept of delayedcount.

   * packages/apps/AicpExtras/
d5ad201 AE: Updated DE translations by Ralf Luther

   * packages/apps/CellBroadcastReceiver/
d6461d6 Correct the broadcast channel for Colombia

   * packages/apps/DeskClock/
d0561ad DeskClock: Initial DE translations by Ralf Luther

   * packages/apps/Dialer/
cd8c0ac Dialer: Updated DE translations by Ralf Luther

   * packages/apps/Messaging/
4cc542b Automatic translation import
ddf7c99 [SMS] Replace message content for protocol 0x41-0x47

   * packages/apps/PackageInstaller/
8e9f5c4 PackageInstaller: Initial DE translations by Ralf Luther

   * packages/apps/Screencast/
1ecd521 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Settings/
4df255d Settings: Updated DE translations by Ralf Luther
82c6d8d Add fastscroll to the Manage applications screen

   * packages/apps/Trebuchet/
93e949f Wallpaper: Allow multiple partners to be loaded

   * packages/services/Telephony/
30f7970 Automatic translation import

   * vendor/aicp/
c177478 Don't dex-preopt Gello
e4671e9 huashan: Adapt to device tree new fragmented structure

   * vendor/cmsdk/
3b88b95 Themes: Don't kill blacklisted launchers on theme change

====================
     05-27-2016
====================


   * frameworks/base/
3f86f84 Automatic translation import

   * frameworks/native/
ea0ee31 dumpstate: add CM version to output

   * packages/apps/Bluetooth/
8a156be Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/CMBugReport/
9ff9513 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/CMFileManager/
1f47310 Fix crash when rotate to landscape without grant permission
7201e71 Remove set as home menu item for secure storage

   * packages/apps/Calendar/
411ad09 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/CellBroadcastReceiver/
eadcfcd Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Contacts/
ffaa045 Automatic translation import
f05914c Contacts : fix FAB when an InCall plugin tab is in focus

   * packages/apps/ContactsCommon/
f759863 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/DeskClock/
5332383 Modded margaritov color picker
6173e6c Add option to set the color of the digital clock widget

   * packages/apps/Dialer/
7092451 Automatic translation import
08cfce9 Alias Dialer's settings activity for use as caller-info settings
d3c031a Fix NPE in caller-info settings migration component
234d4d3 Dialer: Move Smart Options to aicp_strings
ac7e239 Add migrations for CallerInfo related settings

   * packages/apps/Gello/
f4d3ccf Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/InCallUI/
a5416a6 Automatic translation import
6c47523 Fix copy constructor of ContactInfoCache

   * packages/apps/Messaging/
26db7cf Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/PackageInstaller/
5fea008 Show current and new version in install dialog

   * packages/apps/PhoneCommon/
2c6c8d3 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Profiles/
77051de Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Screencast/
1ad771f Fix reference to a renamed string
e66278d Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Settings/
53e0107 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Snap/
b3cfd09 Snap: Update comment to reflect audio focus changes
2bcea7e SnapdragonCamera: Release audio focus when video recording is done
ed07584 SnapdragonCamera: request audio focus before starting video recording
ccd3e81 SnapdragonCamera: Recording screen to be dynamic
02fa448 SnapdragonCamera: Fix the memory leak on view.

   * packages/apps/SoundRecorder/
0023df8 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/ThemeChooser/
bcc2cca Themes: Stop resetting per-app overlays all the time!
64e446a Add RTL support

   * packages/apps/Trebuchet/
cb3431d Automatic translation import

   * packages/providers/DataUsageProvider/
c42d795 Automatic translation import

   * packages/services/LiveLockScreenService/
ba3b4f9 Automatic translation import

   * packages/services/Telephony/
174665f Automatic translation import
21802c3 Automatic translation import
18caa4f Move IMS strings to proper resource file

   * platform_manifest/
9d291b2 Track PackageInstaller locally
414eaad Track DeskClock locally

   * vendor/aicp/
7dcbead vendor_aicp: Add support for LG Optimus G Intl (geehrc)

   * vendor/cmsdk/
0b7ad38 Automatic translation import

====================
     05-26-2016
====================


   * device/cyanogen/msm8916-common/
4920076 msm8916: Remove deprecated overlay
0566d3d msm8916: Add missing trailing \

   * external/DUtils/
1292e27 DUI: Use DocumentsProvider API helper methods [2/2]

   * frameworks/base/
d6d7270 Pie: Disable background in Bare mode
d5fcf8f NetPluginDelegate: Disable SPAM in log
3621ede SystemUI: fix qs pulldown on certain themes
222da5a pm: Use sourcerecord if available for protected app validation.
567cacc SystemUI: improve keyguard with SIM PIN interactions

   * packages/apps/AicpExtras/
16b98ac AE: Dutch Translation

   * packages/apps/CMFileManager/
bbf2266 PickerActivity: Grant read url permission

   * packages/apps/Contacts/
765f3a0 Contacts: only schedule metrics JobService if Ambient exists

   * packages/apps/Messaging/
a29d139 Integrate CallerInfo with notifications

   * packages/apps/Settings/
a114415 DUI: Use DocumentsProvider API for handling custom icons [1/2]

   * packages/apps/ThemeChooser/
54fe34e Themes: Show title of category in browser fragment

   * packages/services/Telephony/
e679846 Switch back to Auto selection if Manual fail's

====================
     05-25-2016
====================


   * cts/
978b415 Merge "DO NOT MERGE ANYWHERE: Update CTS to 6.0R7" into marshmallow-cts-release
63ce966 DO NOT MERGE ANYWHERE: Update CTS to 6.0R7

   * device/qcom/sepolicy/
2772831 sepolicy: Add hand biometrics manager permission
f17f668 sepolicy: Add improveTouch gesture manager permission

   * external/koush/ion/
3bee672 Ion: Ignore get exif rotation exception

   * frameworks/base/
c929acc Merge changes Ia39db96d,I39f3b4f3 into mm6.0
a2d8a0c StatusBar: Do not just define vars...
7071520 Stop adjustConfigurationLw causing sleep/lock.
413fd58 Fix phone crashes after tapping Data Usage in Settings
9a53b54 fw: Move HOME key interception logic to interceptKeyBeforeDispatching
b9f7a65 SystemUI: improve layout of qs detail panel

   * frameworks/native/
0921754 Add dalvik heap/hwui overrides for xxhdpi phone with 3072MB RAM

   * packages/apps/CellBroadcastReceiver/
89bcf56 Enable broadcast channels for Colombia
25e7ce5 Support playing the alert and vibrate until dismissed

   * packages/apps/Dialer/
30f379c Crash Fix When DeepLinkEnabled callback returns to a null Context.
09f96f4 Overflow popup menu may be null when overflow menu button is not null

   * packages/apps/Messaging/
110cdf8 Add handling of MMS Read report.
9da3129 Revert "[SMS] Replace message content can't be replaced"
88b174e [SMS] Replace message content can't be replaced
54374cf Added support for video and audio mms attachments

   * packages/apps/Settings/
cb4e463 Merge changes Ibb866ba5,I9e022162,Ie9ee1dc6 into mm6.0
a30eb35 Settings: Disable cancelable with multi-windows confirm dialog
b62ae9f Settings: Update oem unlocking status with back button
774c086 Settings: Update oem unlocking status when dismiss
be065b1 Fix the memory leak in TetherSettings
0adfcd3 Settings: Allow sorting Applications by size
3a982c6 Settings: Fix possible NPE

   * packages/providers/ContactsProvider/
e78a3c7 Obtain region config from system-property for Contacts pre-loading

   * packages/providers/TelephonyProvider/
f320e09 Support playing the alert and vibrate until dismissed

   * vendor/aicp/
46ecad2 vendor_aicp: Update the Huashan AICP makefile for Marshmallow
4e95ee3 Update ambientsdk version 1.5.11

====================
     05-24-2016
====================


   * frameworks/av/
8f270dc audiopolicy: engineconfigurable: Don't include the example

   * frameworks/base/
e3630c6 Long press StatusBarHeaderView to launch ThemeChooser headers browser
b668bb1 Only call uncrypt when we're encrypted
abd46a6 SysUI: Fix coloring of frame and bolt
32ba0d1 SysUI: Use linear interpolator for battery level
b5223bc SysUI: Allow styling of battery text/charge blend mode
fce47a5 fw: Repurpose PREVENT_POWER_KEY for preventing multiple system keys.
744f84f SystemUI: fix multi touch gestures and extra jank

   * frameworks/opt/telephony/
5d7e5ef Telephony: don't show unsupported transfer on IMS

   * kernel/cyanogen/msm8916/
4f40f27 mdss: livedisplay: Use CABC command chain for CE

   * packages/apps/Contacts/
5391aed Request storage permission for gallery access
91aeaed Contacts : added a flag to track soft vs hard signed out state

   * packages/apps/Dialer/
b9942cd Mark contact info obtained from a lookup provider with remote source-type
e22a004 View Note: removes the ability to make multiple notes for the same call.

   * packages/apps/InCallUI/
4c88dd1 Add attribution for vector drawable
d89acc0 View Note: Use the DeepLinkIntegrationManager method for view note
23f89ec Fixes a crash when trying to take a note in a Conference Call

   * packages/apps/Messaging/
761d4cc Add UI/UX capability to attach a saved video to a MMS message

   * packages/apps/Nfc/
53615bf Merge "Automatic translation import" into mm6.0
caadde0 Merge "NFC: Adding new vendor specific interface to NFC Service" into mm6.0
d95c991 Merge "Revert "Merge tag 'android-6.0.1_r22' of https://android.googlesource.com/platform/packages/apps/Nfc into cm-13.0"" into mm6.0
374ece5 Automatic translation import
44142f7 NFC: Adding new vendor specific interface to NFC Service
c2d2ce8 Revert "Merge tag 'android-6.0.1_r22' of https://android.googlesource.com/platform/packages/apps/Nfc into cm-13.0"
5cf8dca Merge branch 'cm-13.0' of https://github.com/CyanogenMod/android_packages_apps_Nfc.git into cm

   * packages/apps/Settings/
b7e29f3 Merge "settings -> about phone : improve scroll performance" into mm6.0
9074bb4 Settings: Remove redundant definition of SoundSettingsActivity.

   * packages/apps/SetupWizard/
83ad4fa SetupWizard: Ensure language picker is enabled onResume

   * packages/apps/Snap/
94574eb Snap: Use new window manager flag for prevent system keys.

   * packages/apps/ThemeChooser/
fa09a0c Fix headers icon color fill

   * platform_manifest/
622ef82 Revert "qc hals: Add 8937/8953 variants"
55957d0 qc hals: Add 8937/8953 variants

====================
     05-23-2016
====================


   * build/
928c639 qcom: Support 8937/8963

   * device/qcom/sepolicy/
25dd18a Merge branch 'cm-13.0' of CyanogenMod/android_device_qcom_sepolicy into mm6.0
be150b2 sepolicy: Add support for new mdtpd

   * external/android-clat/
8ac9b35 clatd: Fix packet corruption seen with GRO packets

   * external/toybox/
892c602 toybox: Fix netstat crash
baba9cf Merge branch 'master' of https://android.googlesource.com/platform/external/toybox into cm-13.0
17dcbb7 Revert "toybox: Fix build of static executable"
71ddd1f Revert "toybox: find: Fix segfault when using -iname/-ipath with -exec"

   * frameworks/av/
af1fa68 stagefright: Correct Exynos4 stride alignment

   * frameworks/base/
cc70930 SystemUI: Filter out unsupported values off perf profile tile
0e86c0d bootanim: Cleanup
927aac0 frameworks/base: Support for third party NFC features
0dbc9e7 Merge "Themes: Headers overlay support [2/4] - PART (1/2)" into mm6.0
c29881f Fix NL translation after r22 revert

   * packages/apps/AicpExtras/
2518ee6 AicpExtras: improve about_logo performance

   * packages/apps/Gallery2/
d5e574a Gallery: Try to open existing camera

   * packages/apps/Nfc/
6e8f825 NFC: Adding new vendor specific interface to NFC Service

   * packages/apps/Settings/
6422d4a settings -> about phone : improve scroll performance

   * packages/apps/ThemeChooser/
31029f1 Themes: Harden against null bitmaps from provider still processing

   * vendor/aicp/
498250e Merge "Revert "Revert "Include Gello.""" into mm6.0
46b6e7d Merge "Themes: Headers overlay support [4/4]" into mm6.0
820bca1 Revert "Revert "Include Gello.""

====================
     05-22-2016
====================


   * frameworks/base/
976b9d1 fwb: SystemUI: Updated DE translations by Ralf Luther
f646608 IMS: Add support of notifyPreciseCallState for multi sim
de09714 Handle mnc 00 while retrieving the Resources based on subid
6a272f4 Create emergency account with primary stack phone.
821ccbb Add P2 option in openLogicalChannel.
c6f97ef IMS-VT: Disable multi tasking by default
f5d3630 Add 3 APIs for card application

   * frameworks/opt/telephony/
6bbc4f7 WEA: Add an field define for cellbroadcasd table
a3d1585 Update Instrumentation code
82fdcc7 Define EF MSPL/MLPL/PRL values and paths
70d513a telephony: Fix RAT type extra key
939e33a Add iccid support for mvno data
37641df Fix useImsForUt check
dfb34aa Call Forwarding Icon displayed for Deactivated SUB
56693bf Fix Ims pdn deactivate due to single pdn arbitration
93c32a7 Fix to prevent crash on conference failure.
3fed9dd Initialize call state phone app starts
cea18bb Add call reject cause code.
005ab84 Reset internet requests when SIM is removed
962825e Update preferred network type based on active Sub ID
0d51a79 Fix disabled merge button on conference failure.
2f337fb IMS-VT: Update videoProvider in main thread
a4e1e77 FDN: Telephony plugin for SIMRecords
9b4cd40 Make changes to create QtiPhoneProxy class.
d2f1e84 Add pdp data reject with cause code 29 and 33
3e98a2b Add a flag to control SPN display
a2e5603 Telephony plugin for GsmServiceStateTracker
856264a Exclude the last two bytes for the non-type1 Email file.
0fafc4e Specify the path when loading from EF_ADN
aac0a33 Phone App crash: process com.android.phone has stopped.
c30e309 Add p2 option in OpenLogicalChannel
13af2d2 Define telephony resources as a coreApp
b61d381 Telephony: Pass the subId when set data enabled
abb20dc IMS-VT: Update video state of the connection first.
fd4ec5e Move main thread in IPBIM to other thread to fix deadlock.
69cd0a1 IMS: Call forward options with service class support
57e08c2 IMS: handle exception for an invalid service class
6401f6a IMS: During SRVCC, mark dropped incoming call as missed call

   * hardware/qcom/audio-caf/msm8994/
6dafe5c hal: Compilation fixes

   * kernel/cyanogen/msm8916/
1f69f96 video: mdss: remove erroneous mutex_unlock

   * packages/apps/AicpExtras/
80f29f3 AE: Updated DE translations by Ralf Luther

   * packages/apps/Bluetooth/
2a24352 Fix NL translation after r22 revert

   * packages/apps/InCallUI/
0558cad Fix issue of held call disappearing during swap operation.
3dced8d IMS-VT: Animate dialpad on show when InCallActivity re-creates
0a40656 IMS-VT: Set preview surface only if camera is opened
7430539 IMS-VT: Fix camera preview size.
c54f02b IMS: Remove the methods with dummy implementation
54360db IMS-VT: Donot create new surface when setting surface dimensions
f1fdbbf IMS-VT: Trigger internal onStateChanged notification
aaf5d3e IMS: Unbundle capability constant for add participant from frameworks
8acd016 IMS-VT: Unbundle capability consts for downgrade to voice from frameworks
2d638ab IMS-VT: Use correct view size when device is rotated.
94c78cb IMS-VT: Move preview video view after photo view in landscape layout
d129b24 IMS-VT: Catch the exception when dismissing the zoom alert dialog
9b32122 IMS-VT: Update end button position onPreDraw of secondary call info
f8cdd5a IMS-VT: Route to speaker if current route is not BT, headset or speaker
787cdef IMS-VT: Optimize handling of orientation mode.

   * packages/apps/ManagedProvisioning/
dac21a2 Fix NL translation after r22 revert

   * packages/services/Telecomm/
514ad7f IMS-VT: Enable emergency video calls based on mcc/mnc
fc874a0 IMS: Fix vice notifications
aa9b361 IMS: Fix ImsService crash due to default phones not created.
2bf4a6f IMS: Changes for VICE
6a87c56 IMS: Abandon audio focus if no other call exist.

   * packages/services/Telephony/
f49d53e IMS: Fix call forwarding issue in dual sim case
44ab358 IMS: Remove the methods with dummy implementation
9171661 PhoneApp Crash: Multiple times due to permission issue
e24d36e telephony: Fix crash when extended telephony isn't available
31f7a16 Add last call fail cause string.
5975e7b Create emergency account with primary stack phone.
0255fd7 Wrong subid extra name passed to GsmUmtsCallForwardOptions activity
0a4d359 Add p2 option in OpenLogicalChannel
109eb9e Fix merge after a conference call goes through SRVCC.
8606b7f MSIM: Show Enhanced 4G LTE mode option for IMS subscription
60eae21 IMS: Media tag support

====================
     05-21-2016
====================


   * build/
dd62485 build: Fix caf and aospremote

   * device/wileyfox/crackling/
1403778 crackling: ship Gello

   * frameworks/base/
8f538de server: Whitelist non-INTERNET/non-CELLULAR Network for metering
b61c012 keyguard: Fix password doesnot sanitize after verification
962bb1a Revert "SystemUI: recalculate clock position on removing empty shade views"
532e2a9 SystemUI: fix NPE when configuring blur layer
169d8bd Themes: Headers overlay support [2/4] - PART (1/2)
099d4f4 Revert "SystemUI: Add option for new Poly HD custom contextual headers (1/2)"
eb9fe1e Revert "CustomHeader: Full multiuser support for Polly HD"
b3a9bc0f Revert "fix build"
230f16e Merge "Revert "SystemUI: Add new HD poly effect contextual header images"" into mm6.0
337f3c4 Merge "Revert "statusbar: fix poly/original contextual header drawable style change"" into mm6.0
00102f1 Revert "SystemUI: Add new HD poly effect contextual header images"
5f41cf2 Revert "statusbar: fix poly/original contextual header drawable style change"
1426cb8 Merge "Revert "SystemUI: fix clock jumping when expanding QS from lockscreen"" into mm6.0
b6a67e1 Revert "SystemUI: fix clock jumping when expanding QS from lockscreen"

   * frameworks/opt/telephony/
3a3dda6 Add ContentObserver when sms sent limit changed

   * packages/apps/AicpExtras/
a0b45cc Revert "AE: Add option for new Poly HD custom contextual headers (2/2)"

   * packages/apps/CMFileManager/
b0829d6 FileManager : Index all storage volumes

   * packages/apps/Camera2/
96a82ff Camera2: Use new window manager flag for prevent system keys.

   * packages/apps/Contacts/
b897fa4 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Dialer/
a801c25 Automatic translation import
536bea0 Wire up import/export overflow options.
ba2c45b Refactor CallerInfo strings to simplify translations
e523e8c Add negative option to caller info disable dialog
1f6b1d4 Autosize hint text

   * packages/apps/Gello/
1634fa8 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/InCallUI/
0b91346 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Messaging/
7a3ca45 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Screencast/
69c57a7 Refactor audio support

   * packages/apps/Settings/
5e47734 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/Snap/
49caa04 Snap: Restore previous default denoise value
6f0c3b6 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/SoundRecorder/
c5faea1 Automatic translation import

   * packages/apps/ThemeChooser/
1025f8c Themes: Headers overlay support [3/4]

   * packages/apps/Trebuchet/
336be8b Automatic translation import
dccaadb Move icons to fit within Dynamic grid upon resize.

   * packages/providers/ThemesProvider/
e8c46ac Themes: Headers overlay support [1/4]

   * packages/services/Telephony/
b1efa73 Automatic translation import

   * platform_manifest/
327e182 Track Theme package and provider locally
2fe3946 manifest: Gello ships! [2/2]

   * vendor/aicp/
fa598b1 apns: Fix up AT&T APNs
e7f15b2 Themes: Headers overlay support [4/4]
96be653 Revert "Include Gello."
89ed59b Include Gello.

   * vendor/cmsdk/
59be888 cmsdk: Remove unneeded token
18a3869 Themes: Headers overlay support [2/4] - PART (2/2)
6b96494 Automatic translation import
df6259e cmsdk: Skip powersave during testing.
1564e24 Automatic translation import

====================
     05-20-2016
====================


   * device/qcom/sepolicy/
b2acdb1 Merge branch 'LA.BF64.1.2.2_rb4.37' of git://codeaurora.org/device/qcom/sepolicy into cm-13.0

   * frameworks/base/
7b4480b SystemUI: update qs tile hint and header view on locale change
ff3db8d Revert "SysUI: Fix coloring of battery drawables"
2c4db52 Release alarm wakelock for blocked uid.
acd8922 SyncManager: Adjust sync remaining time calculation.
c50b5d9 Themes: Fix theming of cmsdk assets
8544b15 Fix isComponentProtected calls in package manager tests
286a23d MSIM: Fix to resolve SIM PIN unlock in APM.
54cbd8a SystemUI: Check current data subscription when updating signal cluster
fd9a9c3 SysUI: Fix coloring of battery drawables
7cb3cc4 SysUI: Adjust battery dimensions for better look
13b540b Fix Quick settings tiles font themes derp
049a576 am: Handle unchecked activity starts for protected components.

   * frameworks/opt/net/ims/
adbcc1d IMS: Set the correct reason code for merged call
4f42880 IMS: Enhanced 4G LTE mode is turning off IMS.
a973408 Add UT interface to query call forward setting for service class.
65d1461 IMS-VT: Update host call callProfile on conference success

   * frameworks/opt/telephony/
ee21392 SubscriptionInfoUpdater: improved sim swap

   * kernel/cyanogen/msm8916/
75af017 radio: iris: Fix NULL pointer access

   * packages/apps/CarrierConfig/
793e4b4 IMS: Enhanced 4G LTE mode is turning off IMS.
763c36a IMS-VT: Enable multi tasking based on MCC/MNC

   * packages/apps/ContactsCommon/
1d98744 Update LookupRequest to use the new ORIGIN codes within AmbientSDK

   * packages/apps/Dialer/
c404307 Only schedule metrics job if not already scheduled
1f99dd1 Nudges: use unique id instead of packagename

   * packages/apps/InCallUI/
bd76bbb Fix the extra-info container's overlap with dialpad

   * packages/apps/Messaging/
5cf15db Messaging: handle single sim MSIM device
9165168 Use new origin code in LookupRequest

   * packages/apps/Settings/
0c4edbf Settings: Fix Storage Applications Manager dropdown
5f80ff1 Settings: persist "always ask" sms sim selection
2faeb89 Settings : Add title to xml preference screens
]]>
</Changelog>
</ROM>
